Before we start, Spiros and Hiroko, thanks for coming in today to talk about your recent study experiences
在我们开始之前，感谢Spiros和Hiroko能在今天来这里讲讲你们最近的学习经历，
and congratulations to you both in doing so well in your first semester exams!
并祝贺两位在第一学期的考试中取得了好成绩！
I'd like to discuss with you the value of the English for Academic Purposes course you did here last year before starting your university course.
我想与你们探讨在你们上大学之前，去年在这里学的学术英语课程的价值。
Spiros, if I could start with you, what parts of the programme have now proved to be particularly valuable to you?
Spiros，如果可以从你开始的话，项目的哪部分现在证明对你很有价值？
I think that having to do a seminar presentation really helped me,
我觉得研讨会演讲对我很有帮助。
For example, a couple of weeks ago in our marketing subject, when it was my turn to give a presentation I felt quite confident.
例如，几周前当我们的营销专业轮到我演讲时，我感觉很自信。
Of course, I was still nervous but because i had done one before, I knew what to expect.
当然，我仍感到紧张，但是因为我之前做过，所以我知道会发生什么。
Also I know I was well-prepared and I had practised my timing.
而且我知道我准备充分，并练习控制时间。
In fact, I think that in relation to some of the other people in my group, I did quite a good job because my overall style was quite professional.
事实上，我认为相比我们组的其他人，我做得很好。因为我的整体风格都很专业。
What about you, Hiroko?Mmm, that's interesting.
你呢，Hiroko？很有趣。
In my group, I was really surprised by the way the students did their presentations - they just read their notes aloud!Can you believe that?
在我的小组，我对同学们做演讲的方式感到惊讶，他们只是大声地读出他们的笔记！你能相信吗？
They didn't worry about their presentation style or keeping eye contact with their audience -
他们不担心自己的演讲风格，也不和听众做眼神交流。
and I remember that these things were really stressed to us in the course here.
我记得在这里上课时，这些事情对我们都很重要。
So, how did you approach your presentation, Hiroko?
那么，Hiroko，你是如何演讲的？